DE

|

ENG

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

Wiesmann Sports Cars GmbH Privacy Policy  
  
Last updated September 28, 2022  

1 – OVERVIEW OF DATA PROTECTION  
  
1.1 General  
  
The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.  
  
1.2 Data collection on our website  
  
Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?  
  
The data collected on this website is processed by the website operator. The website is operated by Wiesmann Sports Cars GmbH. The contact details can be found in the website's imprint.  
  
How do we collect your personal data?  
  
Some data is collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form.  
  
Other data is collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. This data is primarily technically processed such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. This data is collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.  
  
What do we use your data for?  
  
Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.  
  
What rights do you have regarding your data?  
  
You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, deleted or restricted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the imprint if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.  
  
In addition, you can revoke a consent given by you at any time. The data processing based on the revoked consent may then no longer be continued for the future. Further information can be found under 2.3.  
  
1.3 Analytics and third-party tools  
  
When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be able to identify you from this data.  

2 – GENERAL INFORMATION  
  
2.1 Data protection  
  
Wiesmann Sports Cars GmbH takes the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the GDPR and the national data protection regulations.  
  
If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.  
  
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. For example, this site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.  
  
However, please note that data transmitted via the internet may still be subject to security breaches. Therefore, we have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.  
  
2.2 Notice concerning the party responsible for this website  
  
The responsible for processing data on this website is:  
  
Wiesmann Sports Cars GmbH, An der Lehmkuhle 87, 48249 Dülmen, Germany,  
Phone: +49 (0) 2594 9136 0, Email: [info@wiesmann.com](mailto:info@wiesmann.com "mailto:info@wiesmann.com")  
  
2.3 Your legal rights  
  
2.3.1 Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data  
  
If you have given us your consent to data processing, you may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal e-mail sent to [info@wiesmann.com](mailto:info@wiesmann.com "mailto:info@wiesmann.com") containing the revocation is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your revocation may still be legally processed.  
  
2.3.2 Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities  
  
You have the right to complain to a data protection supervisory authority about the processing of your personal data in our company. For example, you may contact the data protection supervisory authority responsible for us which is:  
  
Landesbeauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit Nordrhein-Westfalen  
Bettina Gayk  
  
Postfach 20 04 44  
40102 Düsseldorf  
  
Kavalleriestraße 2-4  
40213 Düsseldorf  
  
2.3.3 Right to data portability  
  
You may request that we transfer the personal data you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. Alternatively, you may request the direct transfer of the personal data you have provided to us to another controller, where this is possible.  
  
2.3.4 Information, correction, deletion, restriction  
  
As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, deleted or restricted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.  
  
2.3.5 Right to object  
  
Insofar as we process your personal data on the basis of legitimate interests pursuant to Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 lit. f GDPR, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data pursuant to Art. 21 GDPR, insofar as there are grounds for doing so that arise from your particular situation or the objection is directed against direct advertising. In the latter case, you have a general right of objection, which is implemented by us without specifying a particular situation.  

3 – DATA PROTECTION OFFICER  
  
We have appointed a data protection officer for our company who can be directly contacted by sending an e-mail to [info@wiesmann.com](mailto:info@wiesmann.com "mailto:info@wiesmann.com"), or through the contact details stated under paragraph.

3.2. Please add the subject ‘Data protection – personal/confidential’ to each message.  

4 – DATA COLLECTION ON OUR WEBSITE  
  
4.1 Hosting through Shopify  
  
For hosting purposes, we use the services of the service provider Shopify International Limited, Victoria Buildings, 2nd Floor, 1-2 Haddington Road, Dublin 4, D04 XN32, Ireland ("Shopify"). All data collected on our website is processed on Shopify's servers, based on processing on our behalf. In doing so, data may also be transferred to Shopify Inc, 150 Elgin St, Ottawa, ON K2P 1L4, Canada, Shopify Data Processing (USA) Inc, Shopify Payments (USA) Inc or Shopify (USA) Inc as part of further processing on behalf of Shopify. In case of transfer of data to Shopify Inc. in Canada, the adequate level of data protection is guaranteed by adequacy decision of the European Commission. For further information on data protection by Shopify, please visit the following website: [https://www.shopify.de/legal/datenschutz](https://www.shopify.de/legal/datenschutz "https://www.shopify.de/legal/datenschutz")  
  
4.2 Cookies  
  
A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor‘s computer or other internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as a pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server. We may also collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites. The information we collect automatically may include:

• URLs that refer visitors to our websites;  
• Search terms used to reach our websites;  
• Details about the emails we send, such as opens, clicks, and unsubscribes;  
• Details about the devices that are used to access our websites (such as IP address, browser information, device information, and operating system information);  
• Details about your interaction with our websites (such as the date, time, length of stay, and specific pages accessed during your visits to our websites, referral activity, and which emails you may have opened);  
• Usage information (such as the number and frequency of visitors to our websites).

Cookies serve many different purposes, for example, they enable you to navigate our website efficiently, they save your preferred settings and generally improve your visiting experience.

The cookies we use on the website can be divided into the following categories:

**\[CATEGORY OF COOKIES /** WHY WE USE THESE COOKIES**\]**  
  
**Strictly Necessary** / We use these cookies to ensure our site functions properly; they are necessary for our services to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of our services will not work without them. Like the other cookies we use, strictly necessary cookies may be either first-party cookies or third-party cookies.

**Functional** / We use these cookies to remember your settings and preferences. For example, we may use these cookies to remember your language preferences.

**Performance/Analytical** / We use these cookies to count visits and traffic so we can understand, measure and improve the performance of our site. For example, we can use these cookies to learn more about which features are the most popular with our users and where we may need to make improvements. For example, we may use these cookies to determine if you have interacted with a certain page.

**Targeting/ Advertising** / We and our advertising partners use these cookies to deliver advertisements, to make them more relevant and meaningful to you, and to track the efficiency of our advertising campaigns, both on our services and on other websites and social media. These may be used by advertisers to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant ads on other sites.

**Social Media** / These cookies are set by social media services, such as Facebook and Instagram, that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. They do not allow us to gain access to your social media accounts. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of personal data using strictly necessary cookies is Section 25 (2) no. 2 Telecommunications Telemedia Data Protection Act (TTDSG). The cookies are technically necessary to provide the website functions properly that the user wishes to use by accessing the website.  
  
The legal basis for the use of all other cookies, which is not strictly necessary, is your explicit and active consent pursuant to Section 25 (1) TTDSG in conjunction with Art. 6 (1) lit. a) GDPR. The revocation of your consent is possible at any time without affecting the permissibility of the processing until the revocation.  
  
You can view and change your cookie settings at any time in the "Manage cookie settings" section or revoke the consent you have given for cookie use. You can find the section here:

The cookie type can be identified by how long it persists.  
  
Session cookies – these cookies are required only for the duration of your session and are deleted or become invalid as soon as you close our website.  
  
Persistent cookies – these cookies remain on your device for a pre-defined longer period of time (up to one year). They enable you to access our websites more quickly without having to re-configure certain settings, such as your chosen language.  

4.3 Server log files  
  
We collect and store information that your browser  
automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:  
  
• Browser type and browser version  
• Operating system used  
• Referrer URL  
• Host name of the accessing computer  
• Time of the server request  
• IP address  
  
This data will not be combined with data from other sources.  
  
The legal basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. We have a legitimate interest in being able to display the website according to the requirements of your device or browser, and to enable communication between our server and your end device. The data is deleted after 90 days.  
  
4.4 Contact form  
  
Should you send us questions via our contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including the contact details you provide such as first name and surname (optional), email address (mandatory) and your message, to answer your question and any follow-up questions. We do not share this information without your permission.  
  
We will process and store any data you enter onto the contact form only in order to contact you and process your enquiry. The legal basis for the processing of your personal data is the fulfilment of a contract or the performance of pre-contractual measures in accordance with Art. 6 (1) ( b) GDPR.  
  
We will retain the data as long as it is necessary to achieve the purposes for which the data was processed. Any mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain unaffected by this provision.  
  
4.5 Registration on this website  
  
You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here (such as joining the waiting list). The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory information requested during registration (for example, email address) must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your registration.  
  
To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the e-mail address specified during registration.  
  
We will process and store your data provided during registration only for the purpose of making the services available to you. The legal basis for the processing of your personal data is the fulfilment of a contract or the performance of pre-contractual measures in accordance with Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR.  
  
We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.  
  
4.6 Reservation of a car  
  
You may conclude a contract for the reservation of a car on our website in order to be able to purchase the vehicle preferentially at a later date. For this, we ask you to give us your personal data consisting of first name, last name and contact information (email address or phone number). Furthermore, we ask you to provide a billing address to which the invoice should be addressed. This data is mandatory (and therefore partly marked with an asterisk). We will only use the data for the purpose of performing the contract. For example, the contact information will only be used for news related to the reservation of the car, such as to inform you about the possibility to purchase the car.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of this data is the fulfilment of a contract or the performance of pre-contractual measures in accordance with Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR.  
  
Additionally, you have the option to receive further news and offers from us via email or phone call. This requires that you have consented to the use of your data for the transmission of news and offers from us. In order to do so, we ask you to tick the box below your contact information.  
  
The legal basis for processing of your data for this purpose is your consent per Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR. You can revoke your consent at any time, e.g. through an email to [info@wiesmann.com](mailto:info@wiesmann.com "mailto:info@wiesmann.com"). The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.  
  
In the context of payment, we collect some personal data of you and forward the data to our payment service providers in order to process the payment transaction. We use the following payment service providers:  
  
• Apple Pay:  
  
We offer payment via Apple Pay. If you choose the "Apple Pay" payment method of Apple Distribution International (Apple), Hollyhill Industrial Estate, Hollyhill, Cork, Ireland, the payment processing is carried out via the "Apple Pay" function of your device operated with iOS, watchOS or macOS by charging a payment card deposited with "Apple Pay". Apple Pay uses security functions that are integrated into the hardware and software of your device to protect your transactions. In order to release a payment, you must enter a code that you have previously specified and verify it using the "Face ID" or "Touch ID" function of your terminal device.  

For the purposes of payment processing, the information you provide during the ordering process, together with information about your order, will be passed on to Apple in encrypted form. Apple then encrypts this data again with a developer-specific key before the data is transmitted to the payment service provider of the payment card stored in Apple Pay to carry out the payment. The encryption ensures that only the website from which the order was made can access the payment data. After the payment has been made, Apple sends your device account number and a transaction-specific, dynamic security code to the source website to confirm the success of the payment.  

If personal data is processed during the described transfers, the processing is carried out exclusively for the purpose of payment processing in accordance with Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR.  

Apple keeps anonymised transaction data, including the approximate amount of the purchase, the approximate date and time, and whether the transaction was completed successfully.

Anonymisation completely eliminates the possibility of any personal reference. Apple uses the anonymised data to improve Apple Pay and other Apple products and services.  

When you use Apple Pay on the iPhone or Apple Watch to complete a purchase made through Safari on the Mac, the Mac and the authorisation device communicate over an encrypted channel on Apple's servers. Apple does not process or store any of this information in a format that can identify you personally. You can disable the ability to use Apple Pay on your Mac in your iPhone settings. Go to "Wallet & Apple Pay" and uncheck "Allow payments on Mac".  
  
• Google Pay:  
  
We offer payment via Google Pay. If you choose the payment method "Google Pay" of Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, 4 Barrow St, Dublin, D04 E5W5, Ireland ("Google"), the payment will be processed via the "Google Pay" application of your mobile device running at least Android 4.4 ("KitKat") and equipped with an NFC function by charging a payment card deposited with Google Pay or a payment system verified there (e.g. PayPal). For the release of a payment via Google Pay in the amount of more than €25, the prior unlocking of your mobile end device by the respective verification measure set up (such as facial recognition, password, fingerprint or pattern) is required.  

For the purpose of payment processing, the information you provide during the ordering process, together with information about your order, will be passed on to Google. Google then transmits your payment information stored in Google Pay in the form of a uniquely assigned transaction number to the source website, which is used to verify a payment that has been made. This transaction number does not contain any information about the real payment data of your payment means deposited with Google Pay, but is created and transmitted as a one-time valid numeric token. For all transactions via Google Pay, Google only acts as an intermediary to process the payment. The transaction is carried out exclusively in the relationship between the user and the source website by debiting the means of payment deposited with Google Pay.  

Insofar as personal data is processed during the described transfers, the processing is carried out exclusively for the purpose of payment processing in accordance with Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR.  

Google reserves the right to collect, store and evaluate certain transaction-specific information for each transaction made via Google Pay. This includes the date, time and amount of the transaction, merchant location and description, a description provided by the merchant of the goods or services purchased, photos you have attached to the transaction, the name and email address of the seller and buyer or the sender and recipient, the payment method used, your description for the reason for the transaction and, where applicable, the offer associated with the transaction.  

According to Google, this processing is carried out exclusively in accordance with Art. 6(1)(f) DSGVO on the basis of the legitimate interest in proper billing, verification of transaction data and optimisation and functional maintenance of the Google Pay service.  

Google also reserves the right to merge the processed transaction data with other information that is collected and stored by Google when using other Google services.  

The Google Pay terms of use can be found here:  

[https://payments.google.com/payments/apis-secure/u/0/get\_legal\_document?ldo=0&ldt=googlepaytos&ldl=de](https://payments.google.com/payments/apis-secure/u/0/get_legal_document?ldo=0&ldt=googlepaytos&ldl=de "https://payments.google.com/payments/apis-secure/u/0/get_legal_document?ldo=0&ldt=googlepaytos&ldl=de")  
  
• PayPal:  
  
We offer payment via PayPal. PayPal is an online payment service provider. Payments are processed via so-called PayPal accounts. A PayPal account is managed via an email address, which is why there is no classic account number.  
  
If you choose PayPal as your payment method, your data required for the payment process is automatically transmitted to PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l. & Cie. S.C.A., 22-24 Boulevard Royal, 2449 Luxembourg. This regularly involves the following data:  
  
Name, address, company, e-mail address, telephone and mobile number, IP address.  
  
The data transmitted to PayPal may be passed on by PayPal to credit agencies. The purpose of this transmission is to check your identity and creditworthiness. PayPal may also pass on your data to third parties if this is necessary to fulfil contractual obligations or if the data is to be processed on your behalf. You can read PayPal's privacy policy here:

The legal basis for the data processing is Art. 6 (1) b) GDPR, as the processing of the data is necessary for the payment with PayPal and thus for the performance of the contract.  
  
• Shopify Payment  
  
In addition, we offer payment by credit card via Shopify Payments. In order to process your payment, personal data is passed on to the payment service provider Shopify International Limited, Victoria Buildings, 1-2 Haddington Road, Dublin 4, D04 XN32, Ireland.  
  
If you select payment by credit card, the payment data you enter will be transmitted to Shopify International Limited.  
  
This payment method gives you the option to pay by VISA card, Mastercard or American Express card.  
  
VISA (Visa Europe Services Inc. London Branch 1 Sheldon Square London W2 6TT United Kingdom); for further information on data protection, please visit [https://www.visa.de/nutzungsbedingungen/visa-globale-datenschutzmitteilung.html](https://www.visa.de/nutzungsbedingungen/visa-globale-datenschutzmitteilung.html "https://www.visa.de/nutzungsbedingungen/visa-globale-datenschutzmitteilung.html").  
  
Mastercard (Mastercard Europe SA Chaussee de Tervuren 198a 1014 Waterloo); for more information on data protection, please visit [https://www.mastercard.de/de-de/datenschutz/impressum.html](https://www.mastercard.de/de-de/datenschutz/impressum.html "https://www.mastercard.de/de-de/datenschutz/impressum.html").  
  
AMERICAN EXPRESS (Theodor-Heuss-Allee 112 60486 Frankfurt am Main); for further information on data protection, please visit [https://www.americanexpress.com/de/legal/online-datenschutzerklarung.html](https://www.americanexpress.com/de/legal/online-datenschutzerklarung.html "https://www.americanexpress.com/de/legal/online-datenschutzerklarung.html").  
  
The payment processing is handled securely through an external site of Shopify International Limited to fully protect your data.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of this data is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR (processing for the performance of a contract).  

5 – DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA  
  
We will not disclose or otherwise share your personal data with third parties unless this is necessary for the performance of our services or for the protection of our legitimate interest (legal basis of processing: performance of a contract or performance of pre-contractual measures, Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR or protection of legitimate interests, Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR), you have consented to the transfer (legal basis for processing: consent, Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR) or the transfer of data is permitted due to relevant legal provisions (legal basis for processing: fulfilment of legal obligations, Art. 6 (1) lit. c GDPR).  
  
We are entitled to assign the processing of your personal data in whole or in part to external service providers who act as processors for us pursuant to Art. 4 No. 8 GDPR. External service providers support us, for example, in the technical operation and support of the website, data management, the provision and performance of services, marketing and website analysis. The service providers engaged by Wiesmann process your data exclusively in accordance with our instructions. We remain responsible for the protection of your data, which is ensured by strict contractual regulations, technical and organisational measures and additional controls by us.  
  
6 – DATA PROCESSING IN THIRD COUNTRIES  
  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored in third countries (i.e. countries that are neither members of the European Union nor of the European Economic Area) if this is necessary to perform services for you, if it is required by law or if you have given us your consent. Furthermore, there is the possibility that we may also transfer your personal data to processors in third countries or staff operating outside of the EEA who works for us.  
Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by implementing at least one of the following safeguards:

• We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission (such as the European Commission's adequacy decision for the United Kingdom).  
  
• Where we use certain service providers, we may use standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in the EU.  

7 – ANALYTICS AND ADVERTISING  
  
7.1 Google Analytics  
  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. The responsible entity for users in the EU/EEA and Switzerland is Google Ireland Limited, Google Building Gordon House, 4 Barrow St, Dublin, D04 E5W5, Ireland.  
  
Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.  
  
On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website operator.  
  
The data sent by us and linked to cookies are automatically deleted after 26 months. Data whose retention period has been reached is automatically deleted once a month.  
  
You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the storage of cookies for the purpose of using Google Analytics when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
  
7.1.1 IP anonymization  
  
We have activated the IP anonymization feature on this website. Your IP address will be shortened by Google within the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to transmission to the United States. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity, and to provide other services regarding website activity and Internet usage for the website operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with any other data held by Google.  

7.1.2 Browser plugin  
  
You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this website. You can also prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the website (incl. your IP address) from being passed to Google, and the processing of these data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link:  

7.1.3 Objecting to the collection of data  
  
You can prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. An opt-out cookie will be set to prevent your data from being collected on future visits to this site: Disable Google Analytics.  
  
For more information about how Google Analytics handles user data, see Google's privacy policy:  

7.1.4 Outsourced data processing  
  
We have entered into an agreement with Google for the outsourcing of our data processing and fully implement the strict requirements of the German data protection authorities when using Google Analytics.  
  
7.1.5 Demographic data collection by Google Analytics  
  
This website uses Google Analytics' demographic features. This allows reports to be generated containing statements about the age, gender, and interests of site visitors. This data comes from interest-based advertising from Google and third-party visitor data. This collected data cannot be attributed to any specific individual person. You can disable this feature at any time by adjusting the ads settings in your Google account or you can forbid the collection of your data by Google Analytics as described in the section "Refusal of data collection".  
  
7.1.6 Tranfer of data to the US  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found at:  

More information on the handling of user data at Google Analytics can be found in Google's privacy policy:

7.2 Google AdSense  
  
This website uses Google AdSense, a service for including advertisements from Google Inc. ("Google"). It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.  
  
Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies", which are text files stored in your computer that enable an analysis of the way you use the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). Through these web beacons, information such as the visitor traffic on these pages can be evaluated. The data will be deleted automatically after 90 days.  
  
The information generated by cookies and web beacons relating to your use of this website (including your IP address), and delivery of advertising formats, is transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. This information can be passed on from Google to contracting parties of Google. However, Google will not merge your IP address with other data you have stored. As website operator, we can evaluate this data quantitatively by analysing, for example, which search terms have led to the display of our advertisements and how many advertisements have led to corresponding clicks.  
  
You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the storage of cookies for the purpose of using Google AdSense when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly. Please be aware that in this case, you may not be able to make full use of all the features of this website.  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found at:  

7.3 Google Analytics Remarketing  
  
Our websites use the features of Google Analytics Remarketing combined with the crossdevice capabilities of Google AdWords and DoubleClick. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.  
  
This feature makes it possible to link target audiences for promotional marketing created with Google Analytics Remarketing to the cross-device capabilities of Google AdWords and Google DoubleClick. This allows advertising to be displayed based on your personal interests, identified based on your previous usage and surfing behavior on one device (e.g. your mobile phone), on other devices (such as a tablet or computer).  
  
Once you have given your consent, Google will associate your web and app browsing history with your Google Account for this purpose. That way, any device that signs in to your Google Account can use the same personalized promotional messaging.  
  
To support this feature, Google Analytics collects Google-authenticated IDs of users that are temporarily linked to our Google Analytics data to define and create audiences for cross-device ad promotion.  
  
You can permanently opt out of cross-device remarketing/targeting by turning off personalized advertising in your Google Account; follow this link:  

You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the storage of cookies for the purpose of using Google Analytics Remarketing when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found at:  

For more information and the Google Privacy Policy, go to:  

7.4 Google AdWords and Google Conversion Tracking  
  
This website uses Google AdWords. AdWords is an online advertising program from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google").  
  
As part of Google AdWords, we use so-called conversion tracking. When you click on an ad served by Google, a conversion tracking cookie is set. Cookies are small text files that your internet browser stores on your computer. These cookies expire after 30 days and are not used for personal identification of the user. Should the user visit certain pages of the website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and the website can tell that the user clicked on the ad and proceeded to that page.  
  
Each Google AdWords advertiser has a different cookie. Thus, cookies cannot be tracked using the website of an AdWords advertiser. The information obtained using the conversion cookie is used to create conversion statistics for the AdWords advertisers who have opted for conversion tracking. Customers are told the total number of users who clicked on their ad and were redirected to a conversion tracking tag page. However, advertisers do not obtain any information that can be used to personally identify users. If you do not want to participate in tracking, you can opt-out of this by easily disabling the Google Conversion Tracking cookie by changing your browser settings. In doing so, you will not be included in the conversion tracking statistics.  
  
You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the storage of cookies for the purpose of using Google AdWords when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found at:  

For more information about Google AdWords and Google Conversion Tracking, see the Google Privacy Policy:  

You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.  
  
7.5 Google reCAPTCHA  
  
We use "Google reCAPTCHA" (hereinafter "reCAPTCHA") on our websites. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").  
  
reCAPTCHA is used to check whether the data entered on our website (such as on a contact form) has been entered by a human or by an automated program. To do this, reCAPTCHA analyzes the behavior of the website visitor based on various characteristics. This analysis starts automatically as soon as the website visitor enters the website. For the analysis, reCAPTCHA evaluates various information (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor has been on the website, or mouse movements made by the user). The data collected during the analysis will be forwarded to Google.  
  
The reCAPTCHA analyses take place completely in the background. Website visitors are not advised that such an analysis is taking place.  
  
You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the storage of cookies for the purpose of using Google reCAPTCHA when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found at:  

For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google's privacy policy, please visit the following links:  

and  

7.6 Facebook Pixel  
  
Our website measures conversions using visitor action pixels from Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook").  
  
These allow the behavior of site visitors to be tracked after they click on a Facebook ad to reach the provider's website. This allows an analysis of the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes and their future optimization.  
  
The data collected is anonymous to us as operators of this website and we cannot use it to draw any conclusions about our users' identities. However, the data are stored and processed by Facebook, which may make a connection to your Facebook profile and which may use the data for its own advertising purposes, as stipulated in the Facebook privacy policy. This will allow Facebook to display ads both on Facebook and on third-party sites. We have no control over how this data is used. In addition, a cookie is stored on your computer for these purposes.  
  
You may give us your consent (opt-in) for the purpose of using Google reCAPTCHA when you visit our website. The data processing is based on your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time.  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission.  
  
Check out Facebook's privacy policy to learn more about protecting your privacy:  

You can also deactivate the custom audiences remarketing feature in the Ads Settings section at:  
  
[https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry\_product=ad\_settings\_screen](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen "https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen")  
  
You will first need to log into Facebook.  
  
If you do not have a Facebook account, you can opt out of usage-based advertising from Facebook on the website of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance:  

8 – NEWSLETTER  
  
8.1 Newsletter data  
  
If you would like to receive our newsletter, we require a valid e-mail address as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified e-mail address and that you agree to receive this newsletter. No additional data is collected or is only collected on a voluntary basis. We only use this data to provide the newsletter and to inform you about Wiesmann products and news..  
  
We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO. You can revoke consent to the storage of your data and e-mail address as well as their use for sending the newsletter at any time, e.g. through the "unsubscribe" link in the newsletter. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.  
  
The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you cancel your subscription when said data will be deleted. Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. e-mail addresses for the members area) remain unaffected.  
  
8.2 MailChimp  
  
This website uses the services of MailChimp to send newsletters. This service is provided by Rocket Science Group LLC, 675 Ponce De Leon Ave NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA.  
  
MailChimp is a service which organizes and analyzes the distribution of newsletters. If you provide data (e.g. your e-mail address) to subscribe to our newsletter, it will be stored on MailChimp servers in the USA.  
  
We use MailChimp to analyze our newsletter campaigns. When you open an e-mail sent by MailChimp, a file included in the e-mail (called a web beacon) connects to MailChimp's servers in the United States. This allows us to determine if a newsletter message has been opened and which links you click on. In addition, technical information is collected (e.g. time of retrieval, IP address, browser type, and operating system). This information cannot be assigned to a specific recipient. It is used exclusively for the statistical analysis of our newsletter campaigns. The results of these analyses can be used to better tailor future newsletters to your interests.  
  
If you do not want your usage of the newsletter to be analyzed by MailChimp, you will have to unsubscribe from the newsletter. For this purpose, we provide a link in every newsletter we send. You can also unsubscribe from the newsletter directly on the website.  
  
Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time by unsubscribing to the newsletter. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.  
  
The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you cancel your subscription when said data will be deleted from our servers and those of MailChimp. Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. e-mail addresses for the members area) remains unaffected.  
  
The transfer of data to the USA is based on the updated standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission.  
  
For details, see the MailChimp privacy policy at:  

8.2.1 Completion of a data processing agreement  
  
We have entered into a data processing agreement with MailChimp, in which we require MailChimp to protect the data of our customers and not to disclose said data to third parties. This agreement may be viewed at the following link:  
  
[https://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/dataprocessing-agreement/sample-agreement/](https://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/dataprocessing-agreement/sample-agreement/ "https://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/dataprocessing-agreement/sample-agreement/")  

9 – DATA RETENTION  
  
We will only retain your personal data for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or reporting requirements. We may retain your personal data for a longer period in the event of a complaint or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship with you.  
  
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or other requirements.  
  
10 - NO AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING (INCLUDING PROFILING).  
  
We do not intend to use any personal data collected from you for any automated individual decision-making process (including profiling) according to Art. 22 GDPR

Quick links
-----------

* COOKIE SETTINGS

DE

|

ENG

**Wiesmann.com Forms**

* [ ]  Enquiry EN
* [ ]  Waiting List EN
* [ ]  Existing Customer EN
* [ ]  Enquiry DE
* [ ]  Waiting List DE
* [ ]  Existing Customer DE
* [ ]  Pop-up EN
* [ ]  Pop-up DE
* [x]  Newsletter EN
* [ ]  Newsletter DE

© WIESMANN 2024

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
